var list=[
    {   "no":"1",
        "question":"Which film series does 'Dobby' comes from?",
        "choice1":"Harry Potter",
        "choice2":"Percy Jackson",
        "choice3":"The Lord of the Ring",
        "choice4":"Eragon",
        "answer":"Harry Potter"
    },
    {
        "no":"2",
        "question":"Who is Percy's helper?",
        "choice1":"Dobby, elf",
        "choice2":"Grover Underwood",
        "choice3":"Saphira",
        "choice4":"Landroval",
        "answer":"Grover Underwood"
    },
    {
        "no":"3",
        "question":"Which is house of god/goddess that 'Annabeth' comes from?",
        "choice1":"Demeter",
        "choice2":"Dionysus",
        "choice3":"Athena",
        "choice4":"Apollo",
        "answer":"Athena"
    },
    {
        "no":"4",
        "question":"Who is the real lighting theif?",
        "choice1":"Kronos",
        "choice2":"Percy Jackson",
        "choice3":"Hades",
        "choice4":"Luke Castellan",
        "answer":"Luke Castellan"
    },
    {
        "no":"5",
        "question":"Where the new central of Olympus?",
        "choice1":"USA",
        "choice2":"China",
        "choice3":"UK",
        "choice4":"Thailand",
        "answer":"USA"
    },
    {
        "no":"6",
        "question":"Who is vallian in Eragon series?",
        "choice1":"Saphira",
        "choice2":"The King",
        "choice3":"Eragon",
        "choice4":"Shadows",
        "answer":"The King"
    },
    {
        "no":"7",
        "question":"Which point of the dragon that Eragon stand before charging the Shadows?",
        "choice1":"Head",
        "choice2":"Back",
        "choice3":"Tail",
        "choice4":"Paw",
        "answer":"Tail"
    },
    {
        "no":"8",
        "question":"What is creature type of Smeagol before he found the ring?",
        "choice1":"Dwarf",
        "choice2":"Elf",
        "choice3":"Goblin",
        "choice4":"Hobbit",
        "answer":"Hobbit"
    },
    {
        "no":"9",
        "question":"The destination of tortuned elf is?",
        "choice1":"Turn to be Orc",
        "choice2":"Turn to be Nazgul",
        "choice3":"Turn to be Gollum",
        "choice4":"Nothing but pain",
        "answer":"Turn to be an Orc"
    },
    {
        "no":"10",
        "question":"What creatures the Nazguls use to be?",
        "choice1":"Dwarf",
        "choice2":"Human",
        "choice3":"Elf",
        "choice4":"Hobbit",
        "answer":"Human"
    },
    {
        "no":"11",
        "question":"How Hogwarts students transport to their school?",
        "choice1":"By ship",
        "choice2":"By bus",
        "choice3":"By train",
        "choice4":"By broom",
        "answer":"By train"
    },
    {
        "no":"12",
        "question":"What is a spell to lift the feather?",
        "choice1":"Crucio",
        "choice2":"Stupefy",
        "choice3":"Avada Kedavra",
        "choice4":"Wingardium Leviosa",
        "answer":"Wingardium Leviosa"
    },
    {
        "no":"13",
        "question":"Who help Harry Potter from Dementor?",
        "choice1":"Severus Snape",
        "choice2":"James Potter",
        "choice3":"Sirius Black",
        "choice4":"Remus Lupin",
        "answer":"Severus Snape"
    },
    {
        "no":"14",
        "question":"How many campus in Half-Blood Camp?",
        "choice1":"10",
        "choice2":"12",
        "choice3":"13",
        "choice4":"15",
        "answer":"12"
    },
    {
        "no":"15",
        "question":"Who is the most powerful god of Olympus?",
        "choice1":"Hades",
        "choice2":"Hera",
        "choice3":"Zeus",
        "choice4":"Posidon",
        "answer":"Zeus"
    }
]
